Beschrijving van de collection Cornelis Hendrik van Schooneveld
Universiteitsbibliotheek Leiden
- Archives regarding Mouton and related activities (inv. nos. 1-13)., A.
  - Mouton editor's correspondence., 1.; Correspondence, in alphabetical order by name, concerning manuscripts that were earmarked for publication in the Mouton series Slavistic printings and reprintings, Janua linguarum and De proprietatibus litterarum.; 97 boxes.; Every manuscript (in some case th
    - K
      1748. Kachru, B. (Conference on phonology). - 1749. Kachru, Y. - 1750. Kacnel’son, S.D. - 1751. Kacnel’son, S.D. - 1752. Kadić, A. (Croation reader). - 1753. Kadić, A. (From Croation Renaissance to...). - 1754. Kadić, A. (South Slavic culture). - 1755. Kadić, A. (South Slavic culture: essays). - 1756. Kadish, D.Y. - 1757. Kagan-Kans, E. - 1758. Kahn, E. (Foudations of a computable...). - 1759. Kálmán, B. (Wogulische Texte). - 1760. Kaminska, A.B. (Medieval acceptance and revolt in religious confessions expressed with literary art). - 1761. Kaminsky, A.R.. - 1762. Kammann, R. - 1763. Kanaguchi, Y. - 1764. Kandel, M. - 1765. Kanet, R.E. (International Slavic Conf.). - 1766. Kanngiesser, S. - 1767. Kanngiesser, S. - 1768. Kantor, M. - 1769. Kantor, M. - 1770. Kantrowitz, N. - 1771. Kao, D. - 1772. Kao, K.-Y. (The classification of Chinese words). - 1773. Kao, K.-Y. (An East-West philosophical base for semantics). - 1774. Kaper, W. - 1775. Kaplan, D.B. - 1776. Kaplan, F. - 1777. Kappler, R.G. - 1778. Kapterev, N.F. - 1779. Karlinsky, S. - 1780. Karolak, S. (Zagadnienia składni ogólnej). - 1781. Karpinska, M. (Język polski). - 1782. Karpova, S.N. - 1783. Karpova, S.N. (Osoznanie slovesnogo sostava reči doškolnikami). - 1784. Kaševic, V.B. - 1785. Kasher, A. - 1786. Kassai, George (Stylistique comparée du français). - 1787. Kataev, I. - 1788. Katamba, F. (Luganda phonoloy and morphology). - 1789. Katičić, R. - 1790. Katičić, R. - 1791. Katranides, A.A. - 1792. Katz, J.J. - 1793. Katz, R.A. - 1794. Katzer, J. (Free association behavior and human language processing). - 1795. Kaufman, T.S. - 1796. Kaufman, T.S. - 1797. Kaula, D. - 1798. Kavanagh, T.M. - 1799. Kay, M. - 1800. Kay, W.B. - 1801. Kayaloff, J. - 1802. Kaye, A.S. (Chadian and Sudanese Arabic). - 1803. Kayevikberg (On questions and answers in Shakespeare). - 1804. Kazazis, K. - 1805. Kazlauskas, J. (Lietuvių kalbos istorinė grammatika). - 1806. Keane, D. (Dialogic invention: four... theories). - 1807-1808. Keane, L. - 1809. Keenan, E. - 1810. Keenan, E.O. (Collection of articles). - 1811. Keener, F.M. - 1812. Keiler, A.R. - 1813. Keiler, A.R. - 1814. Keiler, A.R.. - 1815. Keller, H.H. (Study of German roots). - 1816-1817. Keller, K. - 1818. Kelly, G.R. - 1819. Kelly, M. Del Roy - 1820. Kemball, R. - 1821. Kempson, R.M. - 1822. Kendall, C.B. - 1823. Kendris, T. - 1824. Kennington, N.L. - 1825. Kenstowicz, M., and C. Kisseberth - 1826. Kent, L.J. - 1827. Keon, C. (Rainer Maria Rilke’s...). - 1828. Kerr, J.F. - 1829. Kestner, J.A. (Jane Austen: spatial structure of thematic variations). - 1830. Ketchian, S. (Anna Achmatova and her creative ethos). - 1831. Key, H.H. (Cayuvava Texts and vocabulary). - 1832. Key, H.H. (Morphology of Cayuvava). - 1833. Key, H.H. - 1834. Khalafallah, A. - 1835. Khokle, V.S. (Aspiration in Marathi). - 1836. Khuli, M.A. (A sample transformational grammar of Modern Standard Arabic). - 1837. Kibel, A.C. - 1838. Kibildis, R. - 1839. Kibrik, A.E. (Metodika polevych issledovanij.). - 1840. Kiefer, F. - 1841. Kiley, F.T. - 1842. Killean, C. - 1843. Killingley, D.H. - 1844. Kilroy, J.F. - 1845. Kim, C.-W. - 1846. Kim, S. - 1847. Kimball, S.B. - 1848. Kimenyi, A. (Studies in Kinyarwanda and Bantu phonology). - 1849. Kimmich, F. - 1850. King, A. - 1851. King, R.D. - 1852. Kinney, A., and M. Wolf (Festschrift for G.B. Harrison on Shakespeare). - 1853. Kinsley, W.B. - 1854. Kinzel, P.F. - 1855. Kiparsky, P. - 1856. Kiparsky, P. (Analogical change). - 1857. Kiparsky, P. (Collected works). - 1858. Kiparsky, P. (Phonological change). - 1859. Kipp, D. (Poetic truth). - 1860. Kirchner, M.E. - 1861. Kirk, P.L. - 1862. vacant. - 1863. Kirschbaum J. M. (Slovak language and literature). - 1864. Kirstein, B. - 1865. Kirstein, B. (Vallader syntax--phrase structure). - 1866. Kirton, E. (The playmaker). - 1867. Kispert, R. - 1868. Kisseberth, C.W. (Proceedings of phonology conf.). - 1869. Kisseberth, C.W. - 1870. Kissin, P.P. - 1871. Kissin, P.P. - 1872. Kittredge, R. - 1873. Kittredge, R., and J. Lehrberger (Sublanguages). - 1874. Klammer, T.P. (The structure of dialogue...). - 1875. Klawitter, R.L. - 1876. Klebovich, I. (Second International Congress of Hungarian Linguists). - 1877. Klein, B.B. (Edgar Allan Poe: paradox and ambivalence as a narrative technique). - 1878. Klein, F. (The Position of the adjective...). - 1879. Klein, S. - 1880. Kleiner, E.M. (Russian nom. pl. in - a). - 1881. Kleinman, N.J. - 1882. Kleis, J.C. - 1883. Kliffer, M. (The Spanish Dative). - 1884. Klima, E.S. - 1885. Klimenko, M. (Sergii of Radonezh - life and work). - 1886. Klimes, L. - 1887. Klimes, L. - 1888. Klimov, G.A. (Očerk obščej teorii ėrgativnosti). - 1889. Klimov, G.A. (Sovietica). - 1890. Kline, E.A. - 1891. Klinger, M.F. (William Hogart and 18th Century Drama). - 1892. Kloss, H. - 1893. Klotz, R.M. - 1894. Knapp, P.A. - 1895. Knappert, J. - 1896. Kneedler, R. (Homo Viator...). - 1897. Knies, E.A. - 1898. Knowles, A.V. - 1899. Knowlton, M.A. - 1900. Kobayashi, E. - 1901. Koch, R.A. (Eugene O’Neill’s Aestetic Expression of Time). - 1902. Koch, W.A. - 1903. Koch, W.A. - 1904. Koch, W.A. (Taxologie). - 1905. Kochman, T.M. - 1906. Kodjak, A. - 1907. Kodjak, A.(ed.) (Pushkin symposium). - 1908. Koehler, L. - 1908bis. Kölver, Bernhard. - 1909. Koen, F.M. - 1910. Koerner, E.F.K. - 1911. Kohler, K. - 1912. Koj, L. (Semantics and Pragmatics). - 1913. Kolb-Seletski, N.M. - 1914. Kolmogorov, A.N. - 1915. Kolšanskij, G.V. - 1916. Komai, A.A. - 1917. Komarov, A.P. (O lingvističeskom statuse kauzalnoj svjazi). - 1918. Komlev, N.G. - 1919. Konishi, H. - 1920. Koo, J.H. - 1921. Koolemans-Beijnen, G.J.W. (Semantic analysis of Russian i, a, no, da). - 1922. Kopman, H. - 1923. Korshin, P.J. - 1924. Kortlandt, F.H.H. -1924bis. Kościuszko Foundation Dictionary. - 1925. Kostis, N. - 1926. Kostka, E. - 1927. Kostomarov, V.G. - 1928. Kostomarov, V.G., and E.M. Vereščagin (Language and culture). - 1929. Kotei, N.A. - 1930. Kotošichin, G.K. - 1931. Kottler, B. - 1932. Kottman, E.J. - 1933. Koubourlis, D.J. (Ninth Annual Southern Conference on Slavic Studies). - 1934. Koubourlis, D. (ed.) (Southern Conference on Slavic Studies, 9th Annual). - 1935. Koutsoudas, A. - 1936. Koutsoudas, A. (Papers of the Rule Ordering Congress). - 1937. Kovalev, V.P. (Sovremennyj russkij literaturnyj jazyk). - 1938. vacant. - 1939. Kowal, M. - 1940. Kozak, J.D. (Principles of ont. and conceq.). - 1941. Kozlik, L.A. - 1942. Kraft, C.H. - 1943. Kragalott, J. (Turkish loanwords in Ivo Andrić). - 1944. Kral, A. (Model of speech mechanism). - 1945. Kramer, K.D. - 1946. Krámský, J. - 1947. Krámský, J. (Papers in general Linguistics). - 1948. Krámský, J. (The word). - 1949. Krauss, M.E. - 1950. Kridl, M. - 1951. Kriesel, R.S. - 1952. Krishnayya, V.S. - 1953. Kroeber, K. - 1954. Krohn, R. - 1955. Krooks, D. - 1956. Krueger, J. - 1957. Kruisinga, E. - 1958. Krupa, V. - 1959. Krupp, K.M. - 1960. Kruševskij, N.V. (Očerk nauki o jazyke). - 1961. Krynski, M.J. (A survey of postwar Polish literature (1944-1959) with special reference...). - 1962. Kryzytski, S. - 1963. Krzyzanowski, J. - 1964. Kubinski, T. (Introduction to the theory of...). - 1965. Kuby, L. - 1966. Kučera, H. (American Contributions II). - 1967. Kučera, H. - 1968. Kučera, H. - 1969. Kučera, H. (Czech phonology). - 1970. Kučera, H. (Adverbial expressions of time in Czech, Russian, and English). - 1971. Kufner, H.L. - 1972. Kuhn, I. - 1972bis. Kuiper, F.B.J. - 1973. Kuiper, K. (Rules of English noun compounds). - 1974. Kuipers, A.H. - 1975. Kuipers, A.H. (Shuswap language). - 1976. Kuipers, A.H. (Squamish, II). - 1977. Kulesov, C. - 1978. Kulkani, B.M. - 1979. Kult, L.E. (A grammar of the basic sentence patterns of American English...). - 1980. Kupcek, J.R. - 1981. Kurath, H. (Selected writings). - 1982. Kurcz, I., A.M. Lewicki, J. Sambo, and J. Woronczak. (Word frequencies in contemporary Polish). - 1983. Kurcz, I., A.M. Lewicki, J. Sambor, and J. Woronczak (Word frequencies in C.S. Polish). - 1984. Kurl, S. - 1985. Kuroda, S.Y. - 1985bis. Kurschatt, F. (Grammatik der littauischen Sprache). - 1986. Kuryłowicz, J. (Collected writings). - 1987. Kutscher, E.Y. - 1988. Kuyk, D. Jr. (Surrational strategies). - 1989. Kuypers, K. - 1990. Kuzminski, A. (Towards a linguistic ontology: a critique of rationalist thought based on George Berkeley’s phenomenology of perception). - 1991. Kuzubova, T. (ed.) (Collected articles of Gleb Struve). - 1992. Kyes, R.L. (Olf phonology). - 1993. Kyes, R.L.
    - L
      1994. La Ban, F.K. - 1995. La Charite, V.A. (Rupture and renewal: perspectives on contemporary French poetry). - 1996. La Drière, J.G. - 1997. La Pointe, F. - 1998. Laar, E.Th.M. van der - 1999. Labib, G. - 2000. Labov, W. (On the use of the present to explain the past). - 2001. Labov, W. (Selected writings). - 2002. Labov, W. (Social stratification of English). - 2003. Labov, W. (Sound change in progress). - 2004. Labrie, R.E. - 2005. Lackowski, P.G. - 2006. Laffal, J. - 2007. Laffal, J. (Concept dictionary of English). - 2008. Lakoff, G. (Collection of articles). - 2009. Lamb, S.M. (Selected articles). - 2010. Lamb, S.M. - 2011. Lamb, S.M. - 2012. Lambert, D.M. (The semantic syntax of metaphor). - 2013. Land, S.K. - 2014. Landa, L.N. (Cybernetics and learning). - 2015. Landa, L.N. (Algorithius and teaching). - 2016. Landa, M.G. - 2017. Landon, G.M. - 2018. Lane, R.C. (Life and work of Tyutchev). - 2019. Langacker, R.W. - 2020. Langdon, M.H. (Conf. on Hokkan languages). - 2021. Langdon, M.H. - 2022. Lange, K.P. (transl.) (Chomsky: Strukturen der Syntax). - 2023. Lange, S., and K. Larsson (Syntactical development of a Swedish girl Embla). - 2024. Langenbruch, T. (Dialectical humour in Kant’s ‘Die Aula’). - 2025. Langendoen, T.D. (Collection of articles). - 2026. Langendonck, W. van - 2027. Langford, T.A. - 2028. Lanigan, R.L. - 2029. vacant. - 2030. Lappo-Danilevskij, A. - 2031. Large, J. (Practical approach...). - 2032. Large, J.W. (Proceedings of the symposium on vocal registers in singing). - 2033. Large, J.W. (Symposium... formants and singing). - 2034. Large, J.W. (Symposium.. vibrato). - 2035. Large, J.W. (Contributions of voice research to singing). - 2036. Larkin, M.T. - 2037. Lash, H.J. (The effect of instruction in...). - 2038. Lass, R.G. - 2039. Last, R.W. (ed.) (Affinities). - 2040. Lastra, Y. - 2041. László, B. - 2042. Lathouwers, M.A. - 2043. Lathrop, T.A. (From Latin to Spanish). - 2044. Lathrop, T.A., and F. Jensen - 2045. Latta, W.C. - 2046. Laufer, A. (Synthesis by rule of a Hebrew idiolect). - 2047. Laughlin, V.L. (The Fabliaux and the naturalistic tradition). - 2048. Launer, M.K. (Elementary Russian syntax: a teaching workbook). - 2049. Laurent, J.-P. - 2050. Lauretis, T. de (Desire and discourse: a structural study of the novels of Italo Svevo). - 2051. Lauter, E.L. - 2052. Lavrov, P.A. - 2053. Law, H.W. - 2054. Lawrence, E. - 2055. Lawrence, E.G. (Aristotle’s theory of definition). - 2056. Lawrence, V.S. (Dialect mixture). - 2057. Lawrence, V.S. - 2058. Lawson, U.D. - 2059. Laychuk, J.L. - 2060. Laycock, D.C. (Problems of dictionary making in...). - 2061. Layton, S.J. (Zamjatin’s neorealism in theory and practice). - 2062. Le Mée, K.W. (Study of five Lais of Marie de France). - 2063. Lea, W.A. (Computer recogntion of speech). - 2064. League, R.D. - 2065. Leahy, R. (The divine plan for salvation in the medieval saints’ legends). - 2066. Leaman E. - 2067. Lebrun, Y. - 2068. Lederer, C.B. (Language and the structure of English). - 2069. Ledkovsky, M. (The other Turgenev). - 2070. Lednicki, W. (Sienkiewicz). - 2071. Lednicki, W. (Festschrift). - 2072. Lednicki, W. (Tolstoy). - 2073. Lednicki, W. (Reminiscenses). - 2074. Ledyard, G.K. - 2075. Lee, B.G. (Linguistic evidence for the priotity of the French text…). - 2076. Lee, C.N. - 2077. Lee, C.M. - 2078. Lee, D.A. - 2079. Lee, E.W. - 2080. Lee, R.C. - 2081. Leeming, H. - 2082. Leggett, B.J. - 2083. Lefkowitz, R.W. - 2084. LeGuillou, J.Y. - 2085. Lehfeldt, W. - 2086. Lehmann, W.P. - 2087. Lehmann, W.P. (Opera minora). - 2088. Lehmann, W.P. (ed.) (Einarsson Festschrift). - 2089. Lehmann, W.P. - 2090. Lehnert (Rucklaufigisches Wörterbuch der englischen Gegenwartsprache). - 2091-2092. Lehrberger, J.J. (Functor analysis of natural language). - 2093. Lehrman, E.H. (Handbook for Russian texts). - 2094. Leiber, J. (Modals and modalities). - 2095. Leibowitz, A.H. - 2096. Leibowitz, J. - 2097. Leibowitz, J. - 2098. Leibowitz, J. - 2099. Leidy, T.A. - 2100. Leighton, L.G. - 2101. Leiva-Merikakis, E. (The poetry of atonement: a study of Georg Trakl). - 2102. Lejnieks, V. - 2103. Lejnieks, V. (The sructure of Latin: an introductory text based on Caesar and Cicero). - 2104. Lekomcev, J.K. - 2105. Lemieux, M. - 2106. Lemke, M. - 2107. LeMoine, R.E. (The anagogic theology of Wittgenstein’s ‘Tractatus’). - 2108. Lencek, R.L. - 2109. Lencek, R.L. - 2110. Lencek, R.L. - 2111. Lencek, R.L., and B.O. Unbegaun (ed.) (Ružičić Festschrift). - 2112. Lengyel, C.A. (Creative self). - 2113. Lengyel, C.A. (Sel. poems). - 2114. Lenski, B.A. - 2115. Lentricchia, F.R. Jr. - 2116. Lentzner, K.R. (Semantic and syntactic aspects of Arabic prepositions). - 2117. Leoff, E. - 2118. Leont’ev, A.A. (Kontekst-1973. Semantika i psichologija jazyka). - 2119. Leopold, W.F. - 2120. Lepinis, A.H. - 2121. Lepinis, A.H. (Der Kritiker Robert Musil). - 2122. Lepschy, G.C. - 2123. Lerner, M.G. - 2124. vacant. - 2125. Lertt, J. - 2126. Lesker, J.H. - 2127. Leslau, W. - 2128. Leslau, W. - 2129. Leslau, W. (Amharic reference grammar). - 2130. Leslau, W. (Comp. dict. of Gurage). - 2131. Leslau, W. (English - Amharic context dictionary). - 2132. Lester, M.P. - 2133. Levelt, W.J.M. (Formele grammatica’s in…). - 2134. Levin, S.R. - 2135. Levin, S.R. - 2136. Levin, S.R. - 2137. Levine, D.E. (The style of morality). - 2138. Levinsky, R. - 2139. Levinsohn, S. - 2140. Levitsky, S.L. (Series Studies in European history). - 2141. Levitt, J. - 2142. Levitt, P.M. - 2143. Levkovskaja, K.A. (Wortstruktur und System der Lexik). - 2144. Levy, A.K. - 2145. Levy, H.M. Jr. - 2146. Levy, J. (Die literarische Übersetzung). - 2147. Lewanski, R.C. - 2148. Lewinson, G. - 2149. Lewis, E.D. - 2150. Lewis, G.E. - 2151. Lewis, M.W. - 2152. Lewitter, L.R. - 2153. Lewkowicz, N.K. - 2154. Ley, H. de (‘Un Enchaînement si singulier...’. Saint-Simon memorialist. essay.). - 2155. Li, C.N. - 2156. Li, C.N. (Computerized bibliography). - 2157. Li, F.C. (Case and communicative function in the use of ba in Mandarin). - 2158. Liberman, A. - 2159. Liberman, A. (Collected Articles). - 2160. Lichačev, D.S. - 2161. Lichtman, C.S. - 2162. Lieb, H.H. - 2163. Lieberman, P. (Articles). - 2164. Lieblich, M. - 2165. Liem, N.D. (Cases, clauses and sentences). - 2166. Ligeti, L. (Researches in Altaic languages). - 2167. Light, R. - 2168. Lightfoot, D. (Natural logic and the moods...). - 2169. Lightfoot, M.J. - 2170. Lightfoot, M.J. (Prosody, and the performance of T.S. Eliot). - 2171. Lillyman, W.J. - 2172. Lim, P. Jr. - 2173. Lindauer, M.S. - 2174. Lindauer, M.S. (Research in psychological aesthetics and the arts). - 2175. Lindauer, M.S. (Research in psychological aesthetics and the arts: a personal collection). - 2176. Lindauer, M.S. (Research in psychological aesthetics and the art: a personal collection). - 2177. Lindblom, B. - 2178. Link, G.M. - 2179. Linskij, S.S. (Ponjatie leksičeskoj normy i leksikografičeskaja praktika). - 2180. Liotta, J.F. (Mill and Cassirer on meaning and reference). - 2181. Lípa, J. - 2182. Liston, J.D. - 2183. Ljudskanov, A.K. - 2184. Llamzon, T.A. - 2185. Lloyd, A. (Anatomy of the verb). - 2186. Locicero, D.P. - 2187. Lockwood, D.G. - 2188. Loesch, K.T. - 2189. Loffler, A.M. (L’emphase dans la presse argentine). - 2190. Loflin, M.D. - 2191. Logan, H.M. - 2192. Long, R. (Readings on tagmemic phonology). - 2193. Long, T.A. - 2194. Longacre, R.E. - 2195. Longacre, R.E. (Grammar discovery procedures). - 2196. Longyear, C. - 2197. Longyear, C.R. - 2198. Loomis, J. (Studies in Catullan vers...). - 2199. Lord, J.B. - 2200. Losic, S. - 2201. Lotman, J. - 2202. Lotman, J. (Analiz poetičeskogo teksta). - 2203. Lotman, J. (Semiotika kino). - 2204. Lotman, J. (Struktura chudožestvennogo teksta). - 2205. Lottridge, S. (N.S. Leskov’s Prolog tales). - 2206. Lotz, J. (Papers in the English verb). - 2207. Lotz, J. (Selected writings (Austerlitz, ed.). - 2208. Lotz, J. (ed.) (Wartenstein conference). - 2209. vacant. - 2210. Lougy, R.E. - 2211. Love, N. (Generative phonology: a case study from French). - 2212. Love, N. (Generative phonology: a case study from French). - 2213. Love, P.L. - 2214. Loveless, O.R. - 2215. Lovell, J.H. Jr. - 2216. Lovenheim, B. - 2217. Lowe, I. (Algebraic Theory of English Pronominal Reference). - 2218. Lowe, P. - 2219. Lowe, P. - 2220. Lowrie, J.O. - 2221. Lowry, E.D. - 2222. Loy, A.S. - 2223. Lozano, A.G. - 2224. Lubin, C.K. - 2225. Luckyj, G. - 2226. Luecke, J.M. (The meter and rhythm of ‘Beowulf’). - 2227. Luelsdorff, P. - 2228. Lugton, R.C. (ed.) (Kerns Festschrift). - 2229. Lukanitsch, R.M. - 2230. Lunt, H. (OCSl Grammar). - 2231. Lunt, H. (ed.) (Karpovich lecture on Russ. hist.). - 2232. Lunt, H. (ed.) (Van Wijk: Paterikon). - 2233. Lupaş, L. - 2234. Luria, M.S. - 2235. Lurja, A.R. - 2236. Lurja, A.R. (Basic problems of neurolinguistics). - 2237. Lurja, A.R. (Collected papers on aphasia). - 2238. Lurja, A.R. (Osoznanie slovesnogo sostava reči...). - 2239. Lurja, A.R. (Recovery of speech and language after...). - 2240. Lyman, T.A. - 2241. Lyngstad, A.(Dostoevsky and Schiller). - 2242. Lyons, E, (Art and artist in The Alexandria Quartet: Lawrence Durrell and the making of fictions). - 2243. Lyra, F. - 2244. Lytle, E. (Junction grammar). - 2245. Lytle, E.G. (Gram. of subord. struc. in English).
    - M
      2246. Maatje, F.C. - 2247. MacCormac, E.R. - 2248. Maché, U.F.J. - 2249. Maciuszko, J.J. - 2250. Mack, D. (Semantic syntax of metaphor). - 2251. Macksoud, S.J. - 2252. Macksoud, S.J. - 2253. MacLeish, A. - 2254. MacNamara, M. - 2255. MacNamara, M. (Structure and style in Maupassant’s novelles). - 2256. Macris, J. - 2257. Macro, A. - 2258. Macuch, R. - 2259. Macura, P. (Pushkin’s works). - 2260. Madruga, H. - 2261. Madvig, D.H. - 2262. Magidoff, R. - 2263. Magliola, R. (The phenomenological approach to literature: its theory and methodology). - 2264. Magner, J.E. Jr. - 2265. Magnus, J.L. Jr. - 2266. Magnuson, K.R. - 2267. Magnusson, U. (Studies in the phonology of the …). - 2268. Magnusson, W.L. - 2269. Magnusson, W.L. - 2270. Magnusson, W.L. (Essays in Indo-European linguistics). - 2271. Maher, J.P. - 2272. Mahl, G. - 2273. Mahler, E. - 2274. Mahlow, E.N. - 2275. Mainwaring, M. - 2276. Major, D. (The acquisition of modal auxiliaries...). - 2277. Makaev, E. - 2278. Makkai, A. - 2279. Makkai, A. (Idiom structure). - 2280. Makkai, A. (Maastricht conference). - 2281. Makkai, A. (Perspectives in modern semantics). - 2282. Makkai, A. (The birth of the poem according to Sándor Weöres). - 2283. Makkai, A., and V. (Linguistics at the Crossroads 1972). - 2284. Makkai, V.B. - 2285. Malaquais, E.D. - 2286. Malécot, A. - 2287. Malécot, A. (Contribution a l’étude de la Forc). - 2288. Malécot, A. (Word inventory and frequency analysis of French conversations). - 2289. Malinowski, A. (Aspects of contemporary Judeo-Spanish in Israel based on oral and written sources). - 2290. Malkiel, J. (Selected articles). - 2291-2292. Malkiel, Y. - 2293. Malkiel, Y. (Genetic analysis of word formation). - 2294. Mallac, G. de - 2295. Malmberg, B. - 2296. Malmberg, B. (Collection of selected writings). - 2297. Maloney, G.A. - 2298. vacant. - 2299. Man, P.M. De - 2300. Manca, M. (Harmony and the poet...). - 2301. Mańczak, W. - 2302. Mandel, J. (Alternative readings in Old English poetry). - 2303. Mann, R. - 2304. vacant. - 2305. Manoliu-Manea, M. (Gramatica comparata a limbilor romanice). - 2306. Manoliu-Manea, M. (Structuralismul linguistic). - 2307. Mantini, L.C. - 2308. Mao, N.K.-Kuen - 2309. Maples, R.J.B. - 2310. Maran, L. - 2311. Maranda, P. - 2312. Marchand, J. - 2313. Marcus, S. (Mathematical poetics). - 2314. Mares, F.V. (Hospodine Pomilut NY). - 2315. Margadant, S.V. - 2316. Margalit, A. - 2317. Marghescu, M. (Le concept de litterarite). - 2318. Markey, T. (A North Sea Germanic reader). - 2319. Markov, V. - 2320. Marković, B. - 2321. Markwardt, A. (Selected Writings). - 2322. Marotti, A.F. - 2323. Marquess, H.E. - 2324. Marr, J.R. (The eight Tamil anthologies: a study in early Tamil literature). - 2325. Marr, N.J. (Abchazsko-russkij slovar’). - 2326. Marshall, G.E. (A review of critical opinion on Stendhal in France: 1815 - 1965). - 2327. Marshall, M.M. (A natural generative phonological analysis of the dialect of Notre-Dame-de Sanilhac). - 2328. Marten, A. - 2329. Martin, J.H. - 2329bis. Martin Jr, Leroy. - 2330. Martin, L.S. - 2331. Maruszewski, M. (Speech and brain: neuropsychology). - 2332. Maruszewski, M., and B. Mroziak (ed.) (Selected articles). - 2333. Marvan, J. (Czech dict.). - 2334. Marvan, J. (Prehistoric Slavic contraction). - 2335. Mason, M.G. (The fiction of Walter Pater). - 2336. Mateene, K. - 2337. Matejić, M. (Serbian medieval literatures). - 2338. Matejka, L. (ed.) (American contributions to the Warsaw Congress: I (Ling)). - 2339. Mathesius, V.J. (A functional analysis of present day English). - 2340. Mathesius, V.J. (Don’t be afraid of English). - 2341. Mathesius, V.J. - 2342. Matilal, B.K. - 2343. Matković, M. - 2344. Matson, D.M. - 2345. Matsuda, T. - 2346. Matteson, E.L. - 2347. Matteson, E.L. - 2348. Matthews, R.J. - 2349. Mattingly, I. - 2350. Maurer, S.H. - 2351. Maxwell, D.V. - 2352. May, C.E. - 2353. May, Jacob L. (On practical aspects of a theory of linguistic performance). - 2354. Mayenowa, M.R. - 2355. Mayenowa, M.R. (Introduction to poetics). - 2356. Mayenowa, M.R. (Selected writings). - 2357. Mayenowa, M.R. (Polish Literary articles). - 2358. Mayenowa, M.R. (Sign, language, culture semiotics conf. 1966). - 2359. Mayer, G.L. - 2360. Mayers, M.K. - 2361. Mayrhofer, M. - 2362. Mazeika, E.J. (A descriptive analysis of the language of a bilingual child). - 2363. Mazour, A.G. (V.O. Kliuchevsky). - 2364. Mazzola, M. (Place of Sicilian in the reconstruction of Proto-Romance). - 2365. McCaffrey, A. - 2366. McCann, G.A. (The Persona: its development in English criticism). - 2367. McCarthy, K. - 2368. McCarus, E. - 2369. McCawley, J.D. (Collection of articles). - 2370. McCombs, M.E. - 2371. McCulloch, A. (Patrick White: a tragic vision). - 2372. McDavid, R.I. - 2373. McDonald, J.L. - 2374. McDonald, J. - 2375. McDonaugh, J.T. - 2376. McDowell, C. - 2377. McGann, J.J. - 2378. McGinley, J. (Logology). - 2379. McGlathery, J.M. (Mysticisn and sexuality). - 2380. McGlatyhery, J.M. (Mysticism and sexuality: the tales of E.T.A. Hoffmann). - 2381. McGrady, H.J. Jr. - 2382. McIntosh, A. - 2383. McIntyre, C.D. - 2384. McKay, J.C. (A guide to reference grammars of the modern standard Romance languages). - 2385. McLaughlin, J. - 2386. McLean, H. - 2387. McLean, S.K. - 2388. McLendon, S.V. - 2389. McLendon, S.V. - 2390. McMahon, W.E. (Hans Reichenbach’s philosophy). - 2391. McMichael, J.L. - 2392. McMillan, James B. (see: 2372. McDavid, R.I.) - 2393. McMillin, A.B, - 2394. McNaron, T.A.H. (Almost a miracle: a study of Shakespeare’s romances). - 2395. McNaughton, W.F. - 2396. McNeill - 2397. McWhorter, O.E. - 2398. Mead, G. (The surrealist image: a stylistic study). - 2399. Mecke, G. - 2400. Medalia, Monique - 2401. Medlin, D.M. - 2402. Mée, K. (A meterical study of five Lais of Marie de France). - 2403. Meehan, V. M. - 2404. Megenney, W.W. (A Bahian heritage: an ethnolinguistic study of African influences on...). - 2405. Mehoke, J.S. - 2406. Mehrotra, R.C. - 2407. Meillet, A. - 2408. Meinrad, H. (Tribus). - 2409. Metcalfe, J.C. - 2410. Mel’čuk, I.A. (Bibliography). - 2411. Mel’čuk, I.A. (Opyt teorii lingvističeskich... modelej ‘Smysl-tekst’). - 2412. Mel’čuk, I.A. (Proposed projects). - 2413. Mel’čuk, I.A. (Toward a formal model of Alutor surface syntax.). - 2414. Melito, I.M. - 2415. Mell, D.C. (A poetics of Augustan elegy). - 2416. Melnichuk, A.C. (Bibliography). - 2417. Mel’nikov, G.P. - 2418. Menges, K. (The Orient as reflected in the dawn of Slavic history). - 2419. Menges, K.H. - 2420. Menzel, P. - 2421. Mercken-Spaas, G. (Alienation in Constant’s ‘Adolphe’: an exercise in structural thematics). - 2422. Merker, R. - 2423. Merrifield, W.R. - 2424. Merrill, T.F. (Poetry and God-Talk: the structure of religious language in literature). - 2425. Mershon, H.M. - 2426. Meščaninov, I.I. - 2427. Meskill, R.H. - 2428. Messing, S.D. - 2429. Messman, F.J. - 2430. Messman, F.J. - 2431. Messner, D. - 2432. Messner, D. (Dictionnaire ibéroromane). - 2433. Messner, D. (Inverse Portuguese dictionary). - 2434. Metcalf, A.A. - 2435. Meulen, B. van der - 2436. Mey, J. (Rasmus Rask studies in pragmatic linguistics). - 2437. Mey, J.L. (Rasmus Rask Studies in pragmatic linguistics vol III). - 2438. Mey, J.L. (Whose language?). - 2439. Mey, J.L. (Whose Language?). - 2440. Mey, J.L. - 2441. Mey, J.L. - 2442. Meyer, G.A. (Dict. of two-word verb in English). - 2443. Meyer, W.C. - 2444. Meyers, J. - 2445. Meyers, J. (George Orwell and ethics of responsibility). - 2446. Meyerstein, P.Z. (Husband’s work: free variation). - 2447. Meyerstein, R.S. - 2448. Meyerstein, R.S. - 2449. Meyn, V.M. - 2450. Meys. W.J. (Compound adjectives in English and the ideal speaker-listener). - 2451. Micallef, J. (Morphological study of... Maltese). - 2452. Michael, J. - 2453. Michalski, A.S. - 2454. Michalski, J. - 2455. Michelson, D. - 2456. Michot-Dietrich, H. - 2457. Miclesen, L.R. - 2458. Mierau, E. - 2459. Mihaescu, H. (Influenta greceasca…). - 2460. Mihaescu, H. (ed.) (Istoria secreta). - 2461. Mihaescu, H. (Limba latina in Sud-estul...). - 2462. Mihailovich, V. - 2463. Mihalchenko, I.S. - 2464. Miko, F. (Gen. struct. of Slovak sent.). - 2465. Miko, F. (Style: structure and system). - 2466. Mikola, T. (Die alten Postpostitionen des Nenzischen). - 2467. Mikuš, R.F. - 2468. Milewski, T. (Langues indigenes de l’Amerique). - 2469. Milewski, T. (Linguistics). - 2470. Milivojević, D.D. - 2471. Milivojević, D.D. (Yugo stories). - 2472. Milivojević, D.D. (Macedonian reader). - 2473. Milivojević, D.D., and M. Matejić (Anth. of Serbian lit.). - 2474. Miller, D.M. - 2475. Miller, E. (The Victorian domestic realists). - 2476. Miller, G.A. (Psychological aspects of semantics). - 2477. Miller, J.W. - 2478. Miller, R.L. - 2479. Miller, S. - 2480. Milligan, T.R. - 2481. Mills, D.L. (Practical parsing algorithms). - 2482. Mills, L.L. - 2483. Millward, C. - 2484. Millward, C.M. - 2485. Miltner, V. - 2486. Minadeo, R.W. - 2487. Mindak, M.B. (Le français de 1700-1784 ou, le portrait d’un peuple par quatre contemporains). - 2488. Mirabeau, R.L. - 2489. Miron, Murray S. Derocher, James E. Patton, Sam M. Pratt, Charles C. (The counting of words...). - 2490. Mirsky, O.S. - 2491. Misra, B.G. - 2492. Misra, V.N. - 2493. Mistrík, J. - 2494. Mitchell, G.R. - 2495. Mitchell, S.O. - 2496. Mitchell, W. - 2497. Moag, J.S. - 2498. Mockler, W.E. - 2499. Moerk, E. L. (Pragmatic and semantic aspects of language development during the...). - 2500. Moessner, L. - 2501. Moffett, O.E. (Lautréamont: a critical bibliography, 1870-1970). - 2502. Mogan, J.J. Jr. - 2503. Moglen, H.S. - 2504. Mogus, M. (History of Croatian phonemic system). - 2505. Mohr, E.V. - 2506. Mok, Q.I.M. - 2507. Mol, H. - 2508. Mol, H. (Fundamentals of phonetics, II). - 2509. Molchova, Ž. - 2510. Molinsky, S.J. - 2511. Mollenhauer, P.K. - 2512. Molnár, G.V. - 2513. Molson, F.J. - 2514. Monaghan, J. (The Neo-Firthian tradition and its contrubution to general linguistics). - 2515. Monga, L. (Sannazar et Belleau). - 2516. Monroe, G.K. Jr. - 2517. Monter, B.H. - 2518. Montgomery, C. - 2519. Moody, L.C. (Aleksandr Solženicyn’s prose: a study of phraseology and characterization). - 2520. Moody, M.D. (A classification and analysis (A sequel to it)). - 2521. Moody, M.D. (Classification and analysis of noun+de+noun). - 2522. Moore, L.H. (Robert Penn Warren and history). - 2523. Moore, T.H. - 2524. Morag, S. - 2525. Morag, S. - 2526. Morais-Barbosa, J. - 2527. Morais-Barbosa, J. - 2528. Moran, R.W. Jr. - 2529. Moravcsik, J.M. - 2530. Morgan, R. Jr. - 2531. Morgan, K.S. - 2532. Morgareidge, C.C. - 2533. Morin, J.-Y. (Aspects méthodologiques du mode d’application des règles syntaxiques). - 2534. Morin, Y.C. (Low-level French phonology). - 2535. Morrison, J.C. - 2536. Moser, C. (Conference on 20th cent. Bugarian lit.). - 2537. Moser, C.A. - 2538. Moser, C.A. - 2539. Moser, H. - 2540. Moser-Verrey, M. (Dualité et contunuité du discours narratif). - 2541. Moses, A.K. - 2542. Mošin, V. (Festschrift). - 2543. Moskov, M. - 2544. Moskovljević, M. - 2545. Moskowitz, A.I. - 2546. Mostovac, M. - 2547. Motolanez, G.R. (Botkin as literary critic). - 2548. Moulton, W.G. - 2549. Mounin, G. - 2550. Mounin, G. - 2551. Mountain, J.A. (The search for an absolute: the influence of F.H. Bradley on T.S. Eliot). - 2552. Moyne, J. - 2553. Moyne, J.A. - 2554. Mufti, Sh. (Cirkessian grammar). - 2555. Mugambi, A.F.M. - 2556. Mulder, J.W.F. - 2557. Mulder, J.W.F. (Syntactic relations). - 2558. Muljačič, Z. - 2559. Muller, M. N. - 2560. Muller-Vollmer, K. - 2561. Mundell, G. (A history of American dialectology). - 2562. Munro, D.A. (Rewrite rules for psychology). - 2563. Munson, W.F. - 2564. Muraki, M. - 2565. Muraviev, P.A. (A.L. Volkonsky: the literary critic). - 2566. Murphy, A.B. - 2567. Murray, M.R. (Unidentifiable utterances...). - 2568. Murray, S. - 2569. Murtonen, A. - 2570. Musial, T.J. (Redemptive wit). - 2571. Musial, T.J. (Redemptive wit: a study of the evolution of Ben Jonson’s dramatic theory).